Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2018
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Composer William David Cooper acknowledges Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Jade Conlee, piano, Kristen Theriault, harp, Emlyn Johnson, flute, Hanna Hurwitz and Will Knuth, violin, Erin Lensing, oboe, Stephen Solook, percussion, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Jessica Wooldridge, bassoon, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Daniel Brottman, horn, Katie Weissman, violoncello, Sycil Mathai, trumpet, Mark Broschinsky, trombone, and Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass after a performance of Cooper's piece Epilogue at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9804.tif (Image-file ubmu0081_103.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain leads Slee Sinfonietta members Michael Matsuno, flute, Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass, Kristen Theriault, harp, Stephen Solook, percussion, and Michael Tumiel, clarinet in a performance of Fernando Munizaga's piece Ondas Primarias at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9805David Mettens.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_104.tif)
- Composer Yotam Haber acknowledges Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Will Knuth, violin, Katie Weissman, violoncello, Christopher Guzman, piano, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, and Emlyn Johnson, flute after a performance of Haber's piece Estro poetico-armonico II at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9807.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_105.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Alyssa Roggow, viola, Kristen Theriault, harp, Tomek Arnold, percussion, Emlyn Johnson, flute, and Katie Weissman, violoncello in a performance of David Mettens' piece Without Air at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9808.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_106.tif)
- Mivos Quartet members Lauren Cauley Kalal, violin, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, Mariel Roberts, violoncello, and Olivia De Prato, violin performing John Harbison's piece String Quartet No. 6 at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC0051Harbison.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_107.tif)
- Mivos Quartet members Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, Mariel Roberts, violoncello, and Lauren Cauley Kalal and Olivia De Prato, violin with composer John Harbison rehearsing Harbison's piece String Quartet No. 6 at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9818.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_108.tif)
- Mivos Quartet members Olivia De Prato and Lauren Cauley Kalal, violin, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, and Mariel Roberts, violoncello performing John Harbison's piece String Quartet No. 6 at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00518.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_109.tif)
- Mivos Quartet members Mariel Roberts, violoncello and Lauren Cauley Kalal and Olivia De Prato, violin with composer John Harbison rehearsing Harbison's piece String Quartet No. 6 at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9821John Harbison.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_110.tif)
- Mivos Quartet members Olivia De Prato and Lauren Cauley Kalal, violin, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, and Mariel Roberts, violoncello performing John Harbison's piece String Quartet No. 6 at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00519.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_111.tif)
- Mivos Quartet members Olivia De Prato and Lauren Cauley Kalal, violin, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, and Mariel Roberts, violoncello performing John Harbison's piece String Quartet No. 6 at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00521.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_112.tif)
- Composer John Harbison coaching Mivos Quartet member Olivia De Prato, violin on Harbison's piece String Quartet No. 6 at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9828John Harbison.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_113.tif)
- Composer John Harbison listening to the Mivos Quartet rehearse his piece String Quartet No. 6 at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9835.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_114.tif)
- Composer John Harbison listening to the Mivos Quartet rehearse his piece String Quartet No. 6 at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9836John H.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_115.tif)
- Mivos Quartet members Olivia De Prato and Lauren Cauley Kalal, violin, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, and Mariel Roberts, violoncello acknowledge applause after a performance of Hilda Paredes' piece Cuerdas del Destino at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00522Mivos Quartet.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_116.tif)
- Mivos Quartet members Olivia De Prato and Lauren Cauley Kalal, violin and Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola acknowledge applause as composer Hilda Paredes hugs Mariel Roberts, violoncello after a performance of Paredes' piece Cuerdas del Destino at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00523Hilda Paredes.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_117.tif)
- Composer Hilda Paredes acknowledges Mivos Quartet members Olivia De Prato and Lauren Cauley Kalal, violin, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, and Mariel Roberts, violoncello after a performance of Paredes' piece Cuerdas del Destino at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00524Hilda Paredes.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_118.tif)
- June in Buffalo staff composers John Harbison, Louis Karchin, and Roger Reynolds talk with Irvine Arditti, violin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00533.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_119.tif)
- Composer David Felder acknowledges Mivos Quartet members Olivia De Prato and Lauren Cauley Kalal, violin, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, and Mariel Roberts, violoncello after a performance of Felder's piece Third Face at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00540David Felder.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_120.tif)
- Composers Louis Karchin and John Harbison at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00545.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_121.tif)
- Composers Louis Karchin and John Harbison at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00549.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_122.tif)
- Composer David Felder talks with composer Roger Reynolds and Irvine Arditti, violin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00551.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_123.tif)
- Composer David Felder and Jonathan Golove, violoncello at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00554.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_124.tif)
- Composers Hans Thomalla and Louis Karchin talk at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00556.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_125.tif)
- Composers Hans Thomalla and Louis Karchin talk at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00557.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_126.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00558.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_127.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor rehearses with Ensemble Mise-En members Kelley Barnett, flute, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass, Hajnal Pivnick, violin, and Josh Perry, percussion at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9843.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_128.tif)
- Composer David Felder and xxx coaching Ensemble Mise-En with Ensemble Mise-En guest Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello in view at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9845.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_129.tif)
- Composer David Felder and xxx coaching Ensemble Mise-En at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9847.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_130.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaching Ensemble Mise-En at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9849.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_131.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Mise-En guests Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello and Irvine Arditti, violin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9850.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_132.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Mise-En guest Irvine Arditti, violin at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9852.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_133.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Brad Lubman, conductor in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9854.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_134.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Brad Lubman, conductor in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9856.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_135.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Brad Lubman, conductor and Ensemble Mise-En guest Irvine Arditti, violin in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9859.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_136.tif)
- J. T. Rinker at the sound board at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9863.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_137.tif)
- J. T. Rinker at the sound board at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9865.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_138.tif)
- J. T. Rinker at the sound board at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9867.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_139.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds leading a seminar with composers Fernando Munizaga, Flannery Cunningham, Yi-Hsien Chan, and Igor Coelho A. S. Marques at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9872.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_140.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds leading a seminar with composers Fernando Munizaga, Flannery Cunningham, Yi-Hsien Chan, and Igor Coelho A. S. Marques at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9873Roger Re.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_141.tif)
- Composer Reilly Spitzfaden coaches Hannah Levinson, viola on his piece Touch at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9875Reilly S.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_142.tif)
- Composer Reilly Spitzfaden coaches Hannah Levinson, viola on his piece Touch at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9876.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_143.tif)
- Composer Dylan Findley coaches Ensemble Mise-En members xxx and Josh Perry, percussion on his piece In the Mind of Energy at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9883Dylan Fi.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_144.tif)
- Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Ito, bass clarinet, and Josh Perry, percussion rehearse Dylan Findley's piece In the Mind of Energy at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9887 Seong A.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_145.tif)
- Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Ito, bass clarinet, and Josh Perry, percussion rehearse Dylan Findley's piece In the Mind of Energy at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9890.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_146.tif)
- Composer Seong Ae Kim coaches Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Ito, bass clarinet and Josh Perry, percussion on her piece #metoo at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Seong Ae Kim mwr.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_147.tif)
- Eric Huebner, piano rehearses Angel Jochi Hernandez-Camen's piece Apanahuiayan at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9904Eric Hue.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_148.tif)
- Composer Angel Jochi Hernandez-Camen coaches Eric Huebner, piano on Camen's piece Apanahuiayan at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9910AngelJoc.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_149.tif)
- Composer Angel Jochi Hernandez-Camen coaches Eric Huebner, piano on Camen's piece Apanahuiayan at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9911.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_150.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Hannah Levinson, viola, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Josh Perry, percussion, and Kelley Barnett, flute in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9917 Moon Yo.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_151.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Hannah Levinson, viola, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Josh Perry, percussion, and Kelley Barnett, flute in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9919.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_152.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Hannah Levinson, viola, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Josh Perry, percussion, and Kelley Barnett, flute in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9920.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_153.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Suehiro, piano, Maria Im, violin, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Yumi Ito, clarinet, and Kelley Barnett, flute in rehearsal of Kai-Young Chan's piece Shimmers in the Shivery Moon at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9929Jai Youn.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_154.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Suehiro, piano, Maria Im, violin, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Vasko Dukovski, clarinet, Josh Perry, percussion, and Kelley Barnett, flute in rehearsal of Ioannis Mitsialis' piece Saturn, the Son of Uranus at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9932.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_155.tif)
- Moon Young Ha, conductor leads Ensemble Mise-En members Yumi Suehiro, piano, Maria Im, violin, Maria Hadge, violoncello, Vasko Dukovski, clarinet, Josh Perry, percussion, and Kelley Barnett, flute in rehearsal of Ioannis Mitsialis' piece Saturn, the Son of Uranus at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9933 Ioannis.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_156.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor leads Signal Ensemble members and guests Irvine Arditti, violin, Kelli Kathman, flute, Olivia De Prato, violin, Vasko Dukovski, clarinet, Oliver Hagen, piano, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, and Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello in rehearsal of David Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00562.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_157.tif)
- Signal Ensemble guest Irvine Arditti, violin marking his music as Signal Ensemble member Olivia De Prato, violin looks on in rehearsal of David Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00563.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_158.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor leads the Signal Ensemble members and guests Irvine Arditti and Olivia De Prato, violin, Kelli Kathman, flute, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, Vasko Dukovski, clarinet, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, and Greg Chudzik, double bass in rehearsal of David Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00564.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_159.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches Brad Lubman, conductor, and Signal Ensemble members and guests Irvine Arditti and Olivia De Prato, violin, Kelli Kathman, flute, and Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola on Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00569.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_160.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor leads Signal Ensemble members and guests Kelli Kathman, flute, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, Vasko Dukovski, clarinet, Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello, and Greg Chudzik, double bass in rehearsal of David Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00574.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_161.tif)
- Signal Ensemble members and guests Rosanna Moore, harp, Bill Solomon, percussion, and Irvine Arditti and Olivia De Prato, violin in rehearsal of David Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00576.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_162.tif)
- Signal Ensemble members and guests Irvine Arditti, violin, Kelli Kathman, flute, Olivia De Prato, violin, Vasko Dukovski, clarinet, and Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola in rehearsal of David Felder's piece Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00577.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_163.tif)
- Brad Lubman, conductor leads Signal Ensemble members and guests Olivia De Prato and Irvine Arditti, violin, Oliver Hagen, piano, Victor Lowrie Tafoya, viola, and Lauren Radnofsky, violoncello in rehearsal of David Felder's Jeu de Tarot at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00581.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_164.tif)